Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide.
Raise the sails and take the helm!
That legendary place?
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary.
Until someone proves it real!
Through it all, through
all the trouble of times!
Through the heartache
and through the pain!
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along!
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything!
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are on the cruise.
We are.
Huh?
Captain Smoker!
A message from headquarters!
I've just received word that Monkey D.
Luffy and his pirate crew are headed
to Log Town from the East Blue.
The bounty on his head has just
been raised to 30 million berries!
30 million berries.
I can't wait to congratulate him.
Sir, this is the pirate that defeated
Don Creek and destroyed Arlong Park!
Shut your mouth.
All your whining made
it collapse in defeat.
I'm sorry, sir. Silence.
Your stress is useless.
You alone dictate the pace of your battle.
Am I wrong?
No, sir.
Then why so tense?
Uh, well,
it's been a long time since I faced a
pirate group of this considerable strength,
sir.
You really have nothing to worry
about under my command has there been
even a single pirate to set foot on this
island without being captured No, sir,
just calm the hell down.
You're screwing up my pacing marine
Reporting sir, I have word that a
pirate group has recently arrived.
You're requested there at
once It must be Luffy's group.
How'd they do that?
I just got this 30 million, huh?
This might actually be interesting
Sir?
Just talking to myself, forget it.
Don't you want to see this, Captain?
Captain, you have to tell
us what your orders are.
No need to.
Sir, do you even know who
this pirate's defeated?
Where's Toshiki?
Sir, she mentioned to me that she
had some things to do this morning,
but that she tried to make
it back in time for training.
Irresponsible, girl.
Where the hell's she go?
Yay!
I got ice cream!
You better slow it down or
you're gonna drop it, okay?
Captain Smoker!
My ice cream!
I am very sorry, sir!
Please don't hurt her!
My daughter shouldn't run!
Please don't hurt me!
I'm sorry!
Please don't hurt us!
I'm sorry.
My silly pants have
eaten all your ice cream.
Here, go buy yourself five scoops.
Let's go. Sir!
Thank you, sir! Thank you!
Have at it, boys!
No need to be shy on my
account! I, Call the Crescent,
hereby proclaim all of your food to be at
service to the future King of the Pirates!
So don't bother trying to hide anything.
Hey?
Who's in charge here?
I think you need to
leave So you're Monkey D.
Luffy
You're not worth 30 million.
I guess you're not worth much more
than my grandma's false teeth.
Don't you dare speak to me that way!
Got it?
Captain Smoker?
He is definitely one of the toughest
Marines we've ever seen in this town.
See, Log Town used to be a hangout
for pirates headed to the Grand Line,
but not anymore.
As soon as Smoker took over,
any pirate that's ever come near this
island has been caught, incarcerated,
and executed.
Smoker is bad.
He's a complete and utter monster.
There are even those who say
he has Devil Fruit powers.
Devil Fruit powers?
That's amazing, Captain.
You captured Luffy all by yourself.
You're a complete idiot.
This isn't Luffy.
Anyone could tell that. Huh?
If this garbage was worth 30
million, I'd become a pirate.
So then where's Luffy?
And what's your hurry?
He'll be here soon enough.
I'm here.
But where's the execution platform?
This looks like the docks. Hey!
Can you help me?
Is he a member of this garbage?
No, I don't think so. Not him.
Hi, I need some help.
Do you happen to know where
they execute people around here?
The platform. Yeah, I know.
I just can't seem to find it.
I haven't seen you before.
This is my first time here on the island.
The town is a whole lot
bigger than Fuchsia Village,
and it's really spread out, too.
So why go to the platform?
Personal quest.
To see where the king of the pirates died.
I guess you don't know. Oh, well. Hold it.
Just follow the smoke, kid.
Great! That way?
I'll see you later!
this really sucks damn i just
want to find the execution
platform but somehow i keep
Getting myself turned around.
I'll find it eventually.
Let's see.
This way.
Gold Roger.
Excuse me, do you work here?
The sign hanging outside said this
place is called the Gold Roger.
How'd it get that name?
Scram.
You should leave.
This isn't a place for
unaccompanied children.
Besides, we're closed
for good starting today.
You're going under?
I'm not going under.
I've decided to shut it down myself.
I'm retiring.
Sorry, I just wanted
to know about the name.
See, I'm looking for the
execution platform, but I'm lost.
Could you tell me the way?
What the heck is that?
Whoa, it's a huge skull!
That is so cool!
Killer Giant,
one of the most feared villains to ever
haunt the waters of the Grand Line.
He sent hundreds of pirates to their
deaths over the course of his life.
But it only took Gold Roger a single
blow to put the behemoth down for good.
Gold Roger killed him?
With lightning speed.
And here's the wound that did it.
Killer Giant was a terrible
waste of human flesh anyway,
but he proclaimed with his dying breath,!
Gold Roger, I take my hat off to you.
You will forever be the
king of the pirates.
Awesome!
Tell me more!
When I'd heard he'd conquered the
Grand Line, I wasn't surprised.
I was happy to hear that he was the one
who finally survived those evil seas, yeah.
On this day 22 years ago, Gold
Roger died on that platform.
And that's how it started.
That's when it all began.
The so-called Great Pirate Era, where
everyone with a boat claims to be a pirate.
But look around this once great town.
I'll bet you won't be able to
find yourself a real pirate.
Nothing here but cowards and scum.
Men brave enough to
make the journey to the
Grand Line have all
disappeared from these waters.
There are no more true pirates
left, that's why I'm closing down!
I'm going to the Grand Line.
Hell yeah, Gold Roger's so cool, he's
exactly how a pirate's supposed to be!
That's why I'm here, to go to the Grand
Line, get my hands on the One Piece,
and then be king of the pirates.
Oh, those are some pretty big words.
Even more so because you're in this bar.
I only said what I meant.
Young man,
if there are still people
like you out there,
should I hold off on closing this place?
I don't know.
It could just be me.
That's right.
It could just be you.
In that case, let's have a drink.
I haven't been in this
good a mood in some time.
Um, I don't drink alcohol.
All right, then how about this?
Let's raise our glasses together.
To the eternal King of the Pirates.
Here's to the King of the Pirates.
Nice catch!
It's an elephant bluefin tuna fish!
That's right.
It must have got mixed
in from the south blue.
I got it with pole and lime.
Just a pole and lime?
Blue fin tuna fish.
Okay, let's go. Lift it.
Right, right.
Hey, hold on a second.
How much for it?
Sell the fish to me.
I got everything I need.
I'm completely prepared for
whatever the sea can throw at me.
There isn't anything Usopp
Brave Warrior can't face now.
Uh, wait a minute.
I think I'm forgetting
something important.
That's it.
A first-class sniper
like myself should really
have a top-shelf pair of
goggles to look through.
I'm gonna get the best pair I can find.
I don't care what they cost,
unless it's more than I can afford.
Super Goggles, here I come!
These are them.
These are the ones.
They're perfect.
Hey, lady!
Those are brand new.
They're the top-of-the-line
model from North Blue Company.
Oh, and the import ship I get them from
only stops here in port once a year.
Hey, don't you have any money?
What's wrong with you?
I can't just give these away.
No, I...
That's right, my backpack.
I'll take those.
Oh, excellent choice.
And what a cute little girl.
I happen to know that these are the only
goggles of their kind on the whole island.
No!
Those are my goggles! Drop them!
You snooze, you lose, Grandpa!
Huh? Grandpa?
Little girl, stop right there!
There is no way you could
possibly think I'm an old man.
I'm more like an older brother, right?
Well, you smell like an old man.
I am not old!
Just give me back those goggles!
I found them first!
They're mine!
Yeah?
You better watch your mouth!
Because I'm friends with the Marines
and I'll get them to beat you up!
The Marines? That's right.
And their captain is a close
personal friend of my family's.
He's kind of like my uncle.
Why, you little... Ha!
I'm a great captain, too!
Our Long Park was destroyed
by these two hands!
I was surrounded by hundreds of fishmen,
and the last thing they ever saw
was Captain Usopp the Incredible!
Doing such amazing and terrible things,
they were glad to quickly meet their end!
Now I have a bounty of 30 million berries
on my head so Marines don't scare me!
Oh, 30 million berries, huh?
That's right!
Papa!
Don't call me Papa.
I'm not your daddy.
I bought a present for you.
Happy birthday, Papa!
Oh, my girl.
Carol, you are absolutely the most angelic
little girl a father could ask for.
I love you so much, Papa.
What's with that girl?
But, Papa,
that silly old man over there was being
mean and trying to jack your present!
Now, now.
Don't say jack, dear.
It's not right.
For a proper young girl.
Are you the gentleman that's been
bothering my adorable little daughter?
No, I just...
There's something else!
There's a bounty of 30 million bears.
Oh, a bounty worth 30 million, huh?
Let's take a look.
Oh, are those the new bad guys?
Yeah, I just picked them up today.
600, 1.3 mil, 700, 30
million, Monkey D. Luffy.
For a first bounty, that's impressive.
Where are you going?
OK, that's not me.
I'm not the guy in the poster.
I was just trying to
pretend to be a bad guy.
Bye bye now.
I'm out of here! Bye! See ya! Crap!
That's you.
Okay, you caught me again.
But just try and lay a hand on
me and you'll see what happens.
My Captain Luffy won't sit idly by
and watch one of his crew in danger.
He's a cold-blooded soulless demon
from the very pits of hell itself.
You can't even imagine the
pain that he can inflict.
You've got your daughter to worry about.
Why risk your life over it?
You're right.
It's not worth it.
Anyone worth 30 million berries on his
head is no ordinary man, that's for sure.
Hoppa, you can beat him,
you're the strongest man ever!
And you're not afraid of anyone.
Darling, I don't have to prove anything.
I just need to get by with
enough to keep us happy.
So long as you think I'm the greatest,
that's all that matters to me, understand?
Hoppa I scared him off just like that?
I guess I don't know how
truly terrifying I am?
Time to flex!
I'm glad you came to your senses fool.
Now give me my goggles and just maybe
I'll let you escape with your life Huh?
Don't worry.
I'm gonna pay for them.
I'm a killer not a thief.
Now give them here He's
letting you go old man.
If I were you I'd be running for my life
Okay, fine.
If that's how you want
it then let's settle
this dispute like gentlemen gentlemen here
A duel?
Yeah, I think I can manage that.
If you win, then the goggles are yours.
Two, three, four, six, 30 pistols!
That's the same number of
guns as Daddy the Father!
It's Daddy the Father!
There's gonna be a duel!
Who can be that stupid?
Daddy the Father?
Everybody knows that
Daddy the Father is the
greatest gunslinger in
bounty hunter history.
Not to mention he's
never lost a duel before.
So what kind of idiot...
Oh, that kind.
Good luck, Long Nose.
We got a whole duck for
you already, so relax.
What the hell just happened?
Why am I dueling this guy?
Simple rules.
Walk ten paces and fire. Okay.
What the hell are you doing? Nami!
It looks like you're facing
Daddy the Father in a duel!
Are you nuts?
You're not helping!
You never have anything nice to say!
You get one shot!
Are you ready?
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
What am I doing? This sucks!
I'm so stupid, there's
no way I can beat him!
And six?
I'm gonna die now.
This can't be happening.
Seven?
I can't believe it.
My adventure is just beginning
and I'm already gonna die.
Who'd have thought it would come to this?
Eight?
Ow!
Oh!
Papa, that was awesome!
You're the best!
That was just pathetic.
What a loser.
I don't think I've ever seen
such a cowardly move in my life.
What were you thinking?
Have you no shame?
I'm cheating during a duel.
You should be ashamed of
yourself, it's pathetic.
I'm so sorry, forgive me.
I'm just really too
scared to die this young.
Killing me would be too
easy for you, right?
So please don't shoot me.
You could just let me go, couldn't you?
No, wait.
Nami, if you want money, my friend
here has tons she can give you.
Please spare me, I'm begging
you, sir. What the hell?
So, now you're cowering behind a woman.
Listen.
No, leave her out of this.
She has nothing to do with it.
I'm the one that got myself into this
situation, and nobody can get me out of it.
It's all on me.
Usopp.
Please, just leave Nami out of it.
Usopp?
Did she just call you Usopp? Yes.
Can't be.
You wouldn't by any chance know a man by
the name of Yasopp of
the Red-Haired Pirates,
would you? Yasopp?
That's my dad's name.
Wait, are you saying that you
and my father are friends?
So then you are his son.
Papa?
I met your dad,
and I've never spoken a single word
to anyone about that fateful day.
Until now, that is.
We met in a hot, dry port of call
on a day very much like today.
Come on, Ensign Masterson.
One shot each.
One, two, three...
Please, finish me off.
There's no reason for me to live anymore.
What are you doing?
Your daughter?
Give it.
I wouldn't expect a
cold-blooded marine like
yourself to be treasuring
something like this.
Guess she must be really special.
And what would a dirty
pirate know about it?
Not much.
You were awesome, Yasopp.
No, I wasn't.
I wounded him instead of killing him.
Still need more practice.
Maybe, but the rest of us
would have been killed.
You took on Daddy Masterson and lived!
Thanks, boss.
Really, I'm glad you let me duel him
instead of just killing him on sight.
It hits the spot.
Hey, you want some marine?
Family, huh?
I could never wrap my
mind around that job.
Is that so?
You know, I've got a son.
His name is Usopp.
Haven't seen him in years, though.
I left him for the sea just when he
started walking why didn't you love him?
it wasn't that I loved him
plenty it's just that I loved
something else more the sea
was calling for me amen brother
Now then,
it may be too late for me to do anything
for my son, and I truly regret that.
But you, your daughter, she deserves
to have a parent with her by her side.
Don't ever let her go
while you have the chance.
Not that I'm the one to talk.
I lost our duel, Yasum!
You can't leave me here like this!
You owe that much to me!
You Marines may have to follow the
rules and do everything by the book,
but the best part about being a pirate
is that I can do whatever I want,
whenever I want.
Later.
Papa, no!
A pirate didn't spare your life!
Tell me it's not true!
Usopp? Wow!
Your father must have been amazing!
He beat Daddy the Father! Usopp? I get it!
I understand why you tell me
that story about my father!
You told me that so I would
try to be more like him!
Huh?
You embarrassed yourself for me!
You put yourself beneath me so I would
know what type of man my father was!
I'll never forget that!
Most people would just bury that
story and never tell it to anyone.
But you, you're not afraid
of anything, even shame.
A coward would never do what you just did.
Carol, your dad is the bravest man alive.
Men who are big and
strong are easy to find,
but the ones who put their honor on the
line for others are one in a million.
I can't.
If I accept your dad's mercy,
it'll only bring him more shame.
I have one choice, and
that is to face my death.
Give me another chance.
I have to prove to myself
that I am not a coward.
A life or death fight.
All right.
Choose the weapon you feel
most comfortable with.
This will be our final duel.
Good.
Now, let's see.
You must hit that
weather vane. What? That?
If you miss.
Right.
You'll shoot me through the heart.
Usopp?
So this shot determines whether
I live or die with honor.
He can't.
There's no way he can shoot
that far with a slingshot.
You've missed.
Please don't kill him, Papa.
Please, no.
I can't shoot him because he
shot right through the crown.
He did it, Usopp! He's right!
Good job!
You're as good a shot as your
old man, and a brave one as well.
Your father will be proud.
Go to the Grand Line.
You'll find him there.
He deserves to see what
his son has become.
Daddy.
You're a pretty good shot, old man.
Thanks.
Later!
Wait, Papa!
Now, Carol, don't say later.
It's bad manners.
Sorry, Papa.
I'm gonna try to be a nice
little girl from now on.
My little age, you're nice enough.
Well, I'm gonna be even nicer.
When people say Daddy the
Father is a disgraced Marine,
at least we'll know the real story.
My father will see me as
a true warrior someday.
You'll see I'll be as brave as daddy the
father, and I will make my father proud.
I know it.
So it's you now, that's no
way to treat a customer!
Especially you're only one.
You don't have a right
to be angry with me?
I didn't turn all the pirates
around here into cowards.
That was a decision they all made
once they got to know me, that's all.
Well, isn't that nice?
So you had a guest.
I think I'd like a taste of rum, old man.
I don't have any for you.
Don't be such a bastard.
Today is a very special day.
Don't you think?
Good stuff.
I can see it like it was yesterday.
The day he was executed.
Like today.
Sticky.
They had him shackled as
they led him down Main Street
towards the square where they
built the execution platform.
He walked through town like
it was a victory parade.
Novenidos to the Wealth.
Goldrorj retains me a Wealth.
And my family will never
Wealth. Fame. Power.
Goldrodj retains me.
This and everything
else life had to offer.
He was facing his final
moments before death,
but he acted like it was his coronation.
Destiny.
Fate.
Dreams.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
Do you have any final words to say?
Would you mind taking these off?
They're beginning to chafe me quite a bit.
Please?
I can't do that.
Where am I going to run?
That's all right.
I guess I'm on my own for this one.
All right, let's get this over with.
Hey, Pirate King!
Tell us where in the hell you've
hidden all of your treasure!
Is it in the Grand Line or someplace else?
You found it, didn't you?
You there, shut up!
The legendary treasure!
The One Beast!
You want my treasure?
Just shut your mouth!
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
You
That's how it all began.
Hey, here's a new wanted poster.
Put it where people can see it.
Captain Smoker, my apologies, sir.
The poster.
That's a Straw Hat.
That kid was Monkey T. Luffy.
There it is.
The place where the greatest
pirate who ever lived died.
And the place where the
great pirate age began.